McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus, 1871-1907 (bulk 1895-1905): Finding Aid TC040
Manuscripts Division
- Series 2: Scrapbooks, 1849-1968 December 19; 25 boxes
  - Scrapbook 13: Barnum & Bailey, American Tour, 1903; 1 box
    - "Her Majesty", unidentified woman. Lillian Schaffer, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 21)
    - Lulu Allen. Phyllis Allen, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 22)
    - Red Guards. White Guards, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 23)
    - Cast of the Spectacle. Exits after the spectacle, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 24)
    - Clown, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 25)
    - Three shots of female rider, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 26)
    - An Arenic Queen. Miss Bertha Clarke. (Equestriennes), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 27)
    - Miss Helen Girard in horse drawn trap, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 28)
    - "Cyclo" man riding bicycle on slanting vertical surface, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 29)
    - Miss Minnie Johnson in horse-drawn trap, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 30)
    - Miss Lillian Schaffer, mounted. Lillian Schaffer standing beside horse, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 31)
    - Grunatho Sisters (7) in costume, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 32-37)
    - Siegriest Silban Troupe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 38)
    - Unidentified female. Lilly Allen, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 39)
    - "Pegasus" champion jumper, ridden by Elmer Brooks, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 40)
    - Assorted circus staff and clowns, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 41-42)
    - Unidentified woman and four dogs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 43)
    - Troupe of female tumblers in ethnic dress, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 43-47)
    - Props crew, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 29, Page 48)
    - Correspondence from Bailey to McCaddon, 1891 July 19; 1 box (Box 29, Page enclosed)
  - Scrapbook 14: McCaddon's Great International Show, 1905 trip abroad and failure, 1 box
    - Managers of circus. McCaddon's Circus grounds, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 1)
    - Ticket wagon of McCaddon's International shows, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 2)
    - Four tents of the McCaddon show. Three tents of the McCaddon show, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 3)
    - Menagerie tent. Sioux Indians, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 5)
    - Two shots of the sleeping cars, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 7)
    - Façade of the side show with McCaddon's Show. Side Show band, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 9)
    - Side show group. Stable men., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 11)
    - Stake gang. Cook house helpers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 13)
    - Stables. Russian Cossacks, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 15)
    - Balloon Ascension. Sioux Indians and Afghans, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 17)
    - Main entrance to McCaddon's International Shows. Advance car for McCaddon's Shows. Façade of side show tents, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 18)
    - News clippings on McCaddon's French Tour failure, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 21-27)
    - Two clippings on Buffalo Bills' trip abroad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 30, Page 29)
  - Scrapbook 15: P. T. Barnum in London, Winter, 1889-1890; 1 box
    - 1889 November 16, Cover of Puck with portrait of P.T. Barnum, 1 box (Box 31, Page 1)
    - 1889 November 30, Cover of Lady's Pictorial with portrait of Mrs. P. T. Barnum, 1 box (Box 31, Page 3)
    - 1890 January 25, page from Puck with portrait of J.A. Bailey, 1 box (Box 31, Page 5)
    - 1889 November 16, cartoon in Puck of Barnum's parade confronting Salvationists for street corner, 1 box (Box 31, Page 7)
    - 1889 November 16, cover of Funny Folks with picture of Barnum on elephants, labeled "Triumphal.", 1 box (Box 31, Page 9)
    - 1889 December 25, cover of Scraps, "A Family Christmas Feast at Olympia" with Barnum, animals, and troupe members, 1 box (Box 31, Page 11)
    - 1889 October 26, Front Page of Topical Times with cartoon of Bailey and Company, 1 box (Box 31, Page 13)
    - Reprints of Nov. 7, 1881, The Pictorial World article on the Ocean voyage of Barnum & Bailey animals to Olympia, also depicting scene from Barnum's great show, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 31, Page 15-19)
    - 1889 November 16, Full length portrait of Barnum in Vanity Fair, while seated and eating. 1. profile, 1 box (Box 31, Page 21)
    - 1886 November 16, Cartoon from Funny Folks depicting Barnum's freaks on London streets. F.O.S. portrait Gallery depicting Barnum, 1 box (Box 31, Page 23)
    - 1889 November 2, cover of Man of the World, featuring Barnum, TQL, seated and holding circular for the greatest show on earth, 1 box (Box 31, Page 25)
    - 1889 November 16, Cover of Ally Sloper's Half Holiday, dealing with Barnum and Bailey shows. Cartoon of Christmas of Barnum and Bailey troupe, 1 box (Box 31, Page 27)
    - 1889 December 7, cartoon from Punch part of which deals with Barnum, 1 box (Box 31, Page 27a)
    - 1889 November 2, cartoon from The Entra'acte, regarding Bailey and caterers. Cartoon, "Santa Barnum Claus", 1 box (Box 31, Page 29)
    - 1889 November 23, cartoon, caption of which mentions Barnum and Bailey show, 1 box (Box 31, Page 31)
    - 1889 November 23, cartoon for Scraps, parodying Barnum and Bailey freak shows to make a political point. A. Sloper's interview with P.T. Barnum, cartoon, 1 box (Box 31, Page 33)
    - 1889 November 16, Ally Sloper's Half Holiday, cartoon part of which deals with Barnum. 1889 November 9 illustration from Sporting Truth, showing Roman chariot racing at Barnum & Bailey show at Olympia, 1 box (Box 31, Page 35)
    - Article on "Nero" and cartoon from The Mirror, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 31, Page 37)
    - 1889 November 11, The London Times, article in favor of Bailey, 1 box (Box 31, Page 39)
    - 1889 November 12, The Evening News and Post, London article on the Greatest Show on Earth, 1 box (Box 31, Page 41)
    - Menu to welcome P.T. Barnum and Co. to England, 1889 November 2; 1 box (Box 31, Page 43)
    - Courier for the Greatest Show on Earth, 1889 November 11; 1 box (Box 31, Page 45)
    - Two tickets to Olympia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 31, Page 46)
    - 1890 February 8, The Illustrated Sporting and Dramatic News (4 pgs.) drawing of Chariot races. Barnum and Bailey at Olympia, article on 3rd page, 1 box (Box 31, Page 47)
    - 1890 February 1, Cover of The Man of the World, featuring J.A. Bailey. "Barnum's Partner.", 1 box (Box 31, Page 49)
    - Barnum's Great Show, Toy Book authorized by Mr. Barnum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 31, Page 51)
    - Small clippings labeled and pasted. Re: Barnum and Bailey show at Olympia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 31, Page 53a-53h)
    - Four programs on cloth, 1889 November 20, for Barnum and Bailey's Greatest Show, 1 box (Box 31, Page 55)
    - Facsimile of above printed in Newspaper, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 31, Page 56-57)
  - Scrapbook 16: Press Clippings re: death of J. A. Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Deals exclusively with J.A. Bailey's death, circumstances surrounding it, and recollections of those who knew him., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 32)
  - Scrapbook 17: James Bailey, 1906; 1 box
    - Letter accompanying resolutions re: Bailey's death by Benevolent Protective Order of Tigers to Mrs. Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 33, Page 1)
    - Resolution re: Bailey's Death by the New York Press Club, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 33, Page 2)
    - Clippings re: Bailey's death, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 33, Page 3-51)
    - Clippings re: death of W.H. Gardner, Circus Agent for Barnum and Bailey, who died soon after Bailey himself, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 33, Page 52-55)
    - Clippings re: contest, by Bailey's distant relatives, of Bailey's will, which left everything to Mrs. Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 33, Page 56-59)
  - Scrapbook 18: Will Contest, J. A. Bailey, 1906-1910; 1 box
    - Seattle Times, 1905. Apocryphal tale of J.A. Bailey's "son" and wife, 1 box (Box 34, Page 1)
    - Articles re: contest of Bailey's will, alleging insanity and undue influence. Will is upheld, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 34, Page 2-40)
    - "Recollections of the World's Greatest Amusement Executive.", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 34, Page 41)
    - Articles on McGinnises (Bailey's Family name), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 34, Page 42-43)
    - McCaddon's telegrams informing of Bailey's death, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 34, Page 62)
    - Telegrams to Mrs. Bailey expressing sympathy in regard to Bailey's death, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 34, Page 63-89)
    - Notes expressing sympathy to Mrs. Bailey re: J.A. Bailey's death, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 34, Page 91-123)
    - Photos of flowers sent to funeral of Bailey by members of the Barnum & Bailey staff, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 34, Page 125)
    - Sympathy cards, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 34, Page 127-139)
    - Poem dedicated to Bailey, "Little Jim", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 34, Page 141)
  - Scrapbook 19: Hemmings and Cooper, etc, 1868-1891; 1 box
    - Courier 1871 announcing Menagerie in Kentucky, 1 box (Box 35, Page 9)
    - Hemmings and Coopers Menagerie and Circus as; Crescent City "Blow" Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 11)
    - Catalogue of Showmen's Stock Bills for sale by Russell, Morgan; As for Caravan, Museum and Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 13)
    - Treatise on Health Giving Amusements, and History and Descript. of Ames' New Orleans Mammoth Menagerie and Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 15)
    - Conversation between three Citizens about the Circus; Check from Hemmings and Coopers Menagerie and Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 17)
    - Grand old Erie Route; Van Amburgh and Co Mammoth Menagerie, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 20)
    - Van Amburgh and Co Colossal Menagerie; JE Warner and Co.'s "Great Pacific", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 21)
    - Seeing the Elephant-JE Warner and Co Menagerie, Caravan and Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 23)
    - Egypt-Van Amburgh and Co Ad., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 25)
    - The Great Shoo Fly Minstrels Variety Troupe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 27)
    - Warner's Dream-Great Pacific Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 29)
    - Great European Circus-Lexington, Kentucky, 1871; 1 box (Box 35, Page 31)
    - Bill Lake's Hippo-Olympiad and Mammoth Circus, 1868; 1 box (Box 35, Page 33)
    - John Robinson's Great Consolidation, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 35)
    - Proclamation by ill Lake, General Orders, No. 1... learning that Ku Klux Klan intend sending armies, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 37)
    - Kirbye's Varieties-various poems and prose, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 39)
    - Kirbye's Varieties-various poems and prose (cont.), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 41)
    - Kirbye's Varieties-various poems and prose (cont.), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 43)
    - Great Mastodon coming to LeRoy, 1871, Hippodrome, 1 box (Box 35, Page 45)
    - Proclamation by Bill Lake, General Order re. Ku Klux Klan, 1968 December 18-19; 1 box (Box 35, Page 47)
    - Adam Forepaugh, Show coming to Chicago, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 47)
    - Adam Forepaugh's Zoological and Equestrian Aggregation Offers... (Ad), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 51)
    - Blank, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 47)
    - A Few Plain Facts; Concert Announcement J.A. Bailey's Minstrel and Variety, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 55)
    - European Circus comes to New England States, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 57)
    - The Rambler Announces Ames; New Orleans Menagerie and Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 59)
    - Adam Forepaugh Circus.. A Word to the Public, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 61)
    - Humbug Show, Fly By Night from NY-Charlie Noyes' Circus and Van Amburgh menagerie, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 63)
    - Impeachment of Bill Lake-Ku Klux Klan, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 65)
    - Challenge that Adam Forepaugh's Zoological and Equestrian Aggregation is the Best on Earth, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 67)
    - Personal letter from Coopers and Whitty announcing arrival of circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 69)
    - Tickets for Hemmings and Cooper's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 71)
    - Catalogue of the Great Sale at Auction of Late William Lake's Hyppo-Olympiad and Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 73)
    - The American Agriculturist: Best Paper, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 75)
    - The American Agriculturist: Beautiful Engravings, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 77)
    - Hyatt Frost announces Van Amburgh and Co, 1870; 1 box (Box 35, Page 79)
    - Adam Forepaugh Show at Lancaster, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 81)
    - 1869 J.A. Bailey Circus Coming to Georgia, 1 box (Box 35, Page 83)
    - 1869 J.A. Bailey Circus Coming to Georgia (cont'd), 1 box (Box 35, Page 85)
    - Billy Nichol's Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 87)
    - 1891 Hemmings and Cooper's Grant Consolidation Shows, 1 box (Box 35, Page 89)
    - 1871 Hemmings and Cooper's comes to Hardin County, 1 box (Box 35, Page 91)
    - 1871 Hemmings and Cooper's at Hopkinsville, 1 box (Box 35, Page 93)
    - Hemmings and Cooper Coming, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 95)
    - Van Amburgh and Co.'s Mammoth Menagerie and Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 97)
    - Champion Article about James Robinson's Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 101)
    - Hyatt Frost Announces Van Amburgh Menagerie, 1870; 1 box (Box 35, Page 103)
    - Hemmings and Cooper at Hopkinsville, 1871; 1 box (Box 35, Page 105)
    - One Day Only Exhibition of Great Eastern Menagerie...and Egyptian Caravan in Kentucky, 1873; 1 box (Box 35, Page 109)
    - The Child's Evening Prayer, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 111)
    - World on Wheels coming...Forepaugh Show, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 113)
    - Great Monarch is Coming to Little Rock, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 115)
    - Forepaugh Show under four mammoth Tents, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 117)
    - Hemmings and Cooper-Largest Menagerie-coming, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 119)
    - James E. Cooper's Grand Consolidated Menagerie, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 121)
    - 1869 Bill Lake's Hippo-Olympiad and Mammoth Circus, 1 box (Box 35, Page 123)
    - What the Press and Public say about P.T. Barnum's Great Show 1872; A World's Fair on Wheels-Cooper's Consolidated Menagerie in Indianola, 1 box (Box 35, Page 125)
    - Cooper's Monster Caravan; Coming of the mastodon-J.E. Warner and Co. Four Big Tent Shows, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 127)
    - World on Wheels-Cooper's Consolidated Menagerie; Forepaugh Coming, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 129)
    - Howe's Great London Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 130)
    - 1878 Letter stating that one of last stands of Howes Great London Circus was sold to Cooper and Bailey, 1 box (Box 35, Page 131)
    - Tickets to Bowes' Great London Circus-hippodrome and to Sangers' English Menagerie, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 133)
    - Old John Robinson's Sketches of Animated Nature, 1872; 1 box (Box 35, Page 168)
    - Bill Lake's Hippo-Olympiad and Mammoth Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 171)
    - Twelve Reasons Why People should go West via St. Louis, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 173)
    - Program for The Great Forepaugh Show, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 35, Page 175)
    - Digest of the Taxes on Privileges for 1873; The Ninth Census of Population of the U.S., 1870; 1 box (Box 35, Page 177)
  - Scrapbook 20: Barnum & Bailey, Ltd., Inventory of the Plant, 1899 April 8; 1 box
    - Advance Advertising Department, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 1)
    - Newspaper Cuts, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 2)
    - Wagons, Tableaux, Cages and Chariots, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 3)
    - Railway Cars, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 4)
    - Railway fittings, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 5)
    - Railway repair Department, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 6)
    - Menagerie and Circus canvas departments, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 7)
    - Seating material, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 8)
    - Circus properties, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 9)
    - Properties menagerie department, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 10)
    - Chandelier department, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 11)
    - Repair and Blacksmith department, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 12)
    - Wardrobes, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 13-15)
    - Harness and trappings, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 16)
    - Stable department, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 17)
    - Baggage horses, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 18-21)
    - Ring, race, jumping & driving horses, stallions, and ponies, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 22-23)
    - animals, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 24)
    - Canvas tents, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 25)
    - Office fixtures, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 26)
    - Side show, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 27)
    - Candy stands material, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 27)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 28)
    - Portable Cages, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page 28)
    - Barnum & Bailey Animals Valuation, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page enclosed)
    - Barnum & Bailey Show Valuation, undated; 1 box (Box 36, Page enclosed)
  - Scrapbook 21: Barnum & Bailey on Tour, 1903-1904 (photographs: only major photos are identified in this list), 1 box
    - Stables. Barnum and Bailey troupe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 1)
    - Clown. Horse and carriage. Four equestrians on one horse, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 2)
    - Ticket wagon and staff. Big top. Equestrian section, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 3)
    - Railroad yard. Ten pony team drawing cart. Lew Graham. C.R. Hutchinson and Dr. W.T. Harper, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 4)
    - Giraffe, monkey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 5)
    - Equestrienne. Band. Freaks. Tumbler, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 6)
    - Elephants, Bandwagon, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 7)
    - Equestrians. Trained dog. Mrs. Watkins, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 8)
    - Two band wagons, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 9)
    - High school horses. "American" wagon. Jos. Arthur. J.T. McCaddon. W.D. Coxey. Whiting Allan. Tody Hamilton, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 10)
    - Peanut Concession. Balancing act. Unidentified ladies, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 11)
    - Clown. Ticket office. Sitting horse, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 12)
    - Hotel Hodges. Group of Indians. Crowd shot. Woman with trick horse, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 13)
    - Unloading railroad cars. Midgets with regular sized men. Elephant ridden by midget family. Tuba and children, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 14)
    - Midgets. Balancers. Equestrians, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 15)
    - Cooper Bailey and Co. grounds. L.E. Cooke. W.H. Gardner, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 16)
    - Bandwagon. Tiger cage, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 17)
    - Man performing trick on bicycle. Men at table. Couple, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 18)
    - Cripples at circus grounds. Clown. Frank Hyatt, superintendent, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 19)
    - Band. Flooded river. Midgets. Dog., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 20)
    - Dan Rice. P.T. Barnum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 21)
    - Bandwagon. Staff. George Conklin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 22)
    - Elephants performing. Tumblers-equestrians?, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 23)
    - Forty horse team. July 4th dinner. Frank (Slivers) Oakley, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 24)
    - J.A. Bailey. Mr. And Mrs. H.L. Watkins, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 25)
    - Charles R. Hutchinson, Treasurer. Clown Bullfight, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 26)
    - Louis E. Cooke, general agent. George Arlington, manager of privileges. Charles R. Hutchinson, Treasurer. George O. Starr, Associate Director. Edward Arlington, Traffic Manager. Wm. H. Gardner, General Agent. Harvey L. Watkins, Assistant Manager. R.F. Hamilton, Gen. Press and Newspaper Contracting Agent, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 27)
    - R.W. Ivers, M.D., Physician. W.D. Coxey, Press Agent. W.H. MacDonald, Press Agent. Mrs. C. White, Costumer. Robert S. Bigsby, Superintendent of Properties and Wardrobe. Sam McClure, Pinkerton Representative. Frank Hyatt, General Superintendent. Charles Andress, Legal Adjuster. R.M. Harvley, Special Agent. Frank Melville, Equestrian Director, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 28)
    - John Stevens, Assistant Treasurer. W.F. Bohrer, In charge of White Ticket Wagon. Frank Ferleman, ticket seller. Charles Carroll, ticket seller and calliope player. Joe Harper, ticket seller Red Wagon. Charles Hummel, ticket seller. Fred L. Grillin, Sideshow Orator. Fred Schemp, ticket seller White Wagon. George H. Messick, ticket seller. Ed Ferleman, ticket seller, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 29)
    - Charles McClean, Superintendent of Canvas. John Burke, 1st Assistant Superintendent of Canvas. Thomas Lynch, Superintendent of horses. George Conklin, Superintendent of Animals. Harry G. Barnum, 24 hour agent. P.J. Stanton, Side Show Openings and Concert Announcements. Ed. C. Hunter, Side Show Orator. Gus Ferleman, Forage Agent. John Flandreau, Head Door Tender. Frank Burns, Contracting Agent, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 30)
    - George Starr. Train wreck with Dead Rhino. (30) Some of troupe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 31)
    - Midget and family. Male-female riding team, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 32)
    - Open air circus. Big Show Main Entrance. Ralph G. Spencer, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 33)
    - Clown. Riders-tumblers? George O. Starr and W.R. McDonald, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 34)
    - Balancing act. High school horses. J.T. McCaddon and C.R. Hutchinson, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 35)
    - Forty horse team. Horses in carriage (2), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 36)
    - Giant and Aztec. Staff. Crowd shots, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 37)
    - Train wreck (2), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 38)
    - Clowns (2). Kangaroo with baby. Two shots of canvas on ground, poles up., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 39)
    - Dog and horse act. Child's balancing act in pyramid, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 40)
    - Gnus harnessed to cart, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 41)
    - "Golden Age of Chivalry" chariot. Midget and family. Woman in ethnic dress, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 42)
    - "Golden Age of Chivalry" chariot. Bandwagon. Elephant reclining on trainer (trick). Shot of women with troupe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 43)
    - Vending stand. Some freaks. Canvas on ground, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 44)
    - Giant and midget. Midget standing in tuba. Giant and midget pony, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 45)
    - Elephant with two ladies. Bailey's Home?, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 46)
    - Staff. Balancing act., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 47)